<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Khoi&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Khoi&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mutable Types as Parameter Defaults - Python - (Source Of Bugs)</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/mutable-parameter-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/mutable-parameter-python/</guid>
      <description>Today I am sharing my lesson learned after some hours debugging then figure out a common mistake which many new python developers like me may be faced with.
What did i do! Here is my simple class to implement a Basket with holding some carts when user checkout.
class Basket: def __init__(self, carts=[]): self.carts = carts def add_items(self, item): self.carts.append(item) Basically a list of cart can be add to Basket when it initiation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MEMO: Amazon ES2 - Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/amazon-ec2-memo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/amazon-ec2-memo/</guid>
      <description>Amazon EC2 is AWS primary web service that provides resizable compute capacity in the cloud.
Amazon EC2 is allows you to acquire compute through the lanching of viturak servers call instances.
Instance Types Instance Types defines the vitural hardware supporting an Amazon EC2 instance.
There are many instance types available follow these dimension.
 vCPU Memory Storage (Size/Type) Network perormance Instance types are group into families base on the ratio of these values to each other  Amazon Machine Images (AMIs).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MEMO: Amazon S3 - Amazon Simple Storage Service</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/amazon-s3-memo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/amazon-s3-memo/</guid>
      <description>What is S3.  Save place to store your files. Is a object-base storage. The object is spread across multiple devices and facilities.  The basic of S3. Buckets  A bucket is a container of objects stored in Amazon S3. Every object is contained in a Bucket. Bucket name is a univeral namespace. That is, name must be unique globally. Each bucket created in a specific region.  Objects  Object are the entities or files stored in S3 bucket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Refactoring Strategy Pattern Swift</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:08:29 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/strategy/</guid>
      <description>Problem An Example of strategy applies to the eCommerce, domain is computed discounts to other base on the behavior of the customer, attributes of ordered items. A clear Example of Strategy applied in getting discount on food delivery order. Example: Oder food delivery with some discount rule:
 Discount 10% for User have 100 or more grab reward point. Discount 5$ apply to order with price total 100$ or more. Discount 7% apply to order have at least 10 distinct items  UML class diagram implements strategy pattern</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>